<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>some tag on Basement Bar</title>
    <link>https://basement-bar.net/tags/some-tag/</link>
    <description>Recent content in some tag on Basement Bar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://basement-bar.net/tags/some-tag/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cell Phone Windshield Mount</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/cell-phone-windshield-mount/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/cell-phone-windshield-mount/</guid>
      <description>A cell phone windshield mount is a device that is mounted on the dashboard of a car and is used to hold a cell phone.
** The Best Cell Phone Windshield Mount **
Suction Cup Car Phone Holder Mount, Dashboard/Windshield/Window Phone Holder for Car with Ultra Sticky Gel Pad, Compatible with iPhone, Samsung, 4-6.8 Inch Cellphone, Thick Case &amp;amp; Big Phone Friendly iOttie Easy One Touch 4 Dash &amp;amp; Windshield Universal Car Mount Phone Holder Desk Stand for iPhone, Samsung, Moto, Huawei, Nokia, LG, Smartphones, Black Suction Cup Phone Holder for Windshield/Dashboard/Window, Universal Dashboard &amp;amp; Windshield Sturdy Suction Cup Car Phone Mount with Strong Sticky Gel Pad, Compatible W/ iPhone, Samsung &amp;amp;Other Cellphone 3-in-1 Suction Cup Phone Holder Windshield/Dashboard/Air Vent, Oqtiq Dashboard &amp;amp; Windshield Suction Cup Car Phone Mount with Strong Sticky Gel Pad, Compatible with iPhone, Samsung &amp;amp; Other Cellphone Solid Car Truck Phone Mount Holder with 14-Inch Gooseneck Long Arm, 1Zero Windshield Window Mobile Holders w/ Industrial-Strength Suction Cup, Anti-Shake Stabilizer Compatible All Cell Phones iPhone VICSEED Car Phone Mount, [Thick Case &amp;amp; Big Phones Friendly] Long Arm Suction Cup Phone Holder for Car Dashboard Windshield Air Vent Hands Free Clip Cell Phone Holder Compatible with All Mobile Phones Magnetic Phone Car Mount,APPS2Car Universal Dashboard Windshield Industrial-Strength Suction Cup Car Phone Mount Holder with Adjustable Telescopic Arm,6 Strong Magnets,for All Cell Phones Windshield Car Phone Holder Mount, 13&amp;quot; Suction Cup Phone Holder for Dashboard, Gooseneck Truck Cell Phone Holder for Car, Phone Mount for Dashboard with One Hand Operation, Compatible with All Phones YRU Cell Phone Holder Mount, [Anti-Scratch Silicone &amp;amp; Cable Management] Car Phone Holder Mount Stand Dashboard Windshield Air Vent, Handsfree Phone Cradles Compatible with iPhone 13 12 11 Samsung S21 VANMASS Phone Mount for Car [Auto Hug Tight] Cell Phone Car Mount Safest Guard Ever, Original One Hand Operation [Longest Life] Firmly Hold Dash Vent Windshield Fit for iPhone 13 Samsung All Phones Suction Cup Car Phone Holder Mount, Dashboard/Windshield/Window Phone Holder for Car with Ultra Sticky Gel Pad, Compatible with iPhone, Samsung, 4-6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dvd Lens Cleaner</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/dvd-lens-cleaner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/dvd-lens-cleaner/</guid>
      <description>A DVD lens cleaner is a small, circular disc that is inserted into the DVD player. It is used to clean the lens of the DVD player.
** The Best Dvd Lens Cleaner **
Maxell 190059 DVD Only Lens Cleaner, with Equipment Set Up and Enhancement Features, Packaging May Vary Maxell Safe and Effective Feature CD Player and Game Station Compact Disc Cleaner CD-340 190048 CD/CD-ROM Laser Lens Cleaner - CD Lens Cleaner Memorex CD/DVD Lens Cleaner Arsvita CD Laser Lens Cleaner Disc Cleaning Set for CD/VCD/DVD Player, Safe and Effective Arsvita Laser Lens Cleaner Disc Cleaning Set for CD / VCD / DVD Player, Safe and Effective, ARCD-04 Nicer CD/VCD/DVD Player Cleaner Kit, Laser Lens Cleaning Disc with Double Brush Cleaning System, Set 2 Mwin CD Cleaner Disc for CD Player, Safe and Effective Laser Lens Cleaning Disc, CD/VCD/DVD Player Lens Cleaner Set for Car and Home YHDD CD Cleaner Disc, Safe and Effective CD Lens Cleaner, Laser Lens Cleaning Set for CD/VCD/DVD Player Cd And Dvd Lens Cleaner Digital Innovations CleanDr for Blu-Ray Laser Lens Cleaner for Blu-Ray / DVD / PS3 / PS4 / XBOX / XBOX 360 / XBOX ONE (4190300) Maxell 190059 DVD Only Lens Cleaner, with Equipment Set Up and Enhancement Features, Packaging May Vary386 ReviewsDesigned for DVD players Features Thunderon Brush System Equipment set up and enhancement features (ideal for home theater) Interactive on-screen instructions with 8 languages The 3 small holes contain small brushes which create a static charge to which dust is attracted, when spinning inside the drive being cleaned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emu Oil For Hair</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/emu-oil-for-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/emu-oil-for-hair/</guid>
      <description>Emu oil is a natural oil that is extracted from the fat of the emu bird. It is a popular ingredient in many hair products because it is a natural moisturizer that is also rich in omega-3 and omega-6 fatty acids. Emu oil is also a natural anti-inflammatory and anti-bacterial agent.
The Best Emu Oil For Hair
Emu Oil by Leven Rose, 100% Pure Natural Hair Strengthener Scar Minimizer Anti Aging Skin Moisturizer 4 oz Pure Australian Emu Oil - All Natural 6X Refined for Face, Skin and Hair - Highly Effective Hydration for Sensitive Skin and Hair Growth - Perfect for Scars and Blemishes - Naturally rich and balanced in essential omega 3, 6 and 9 fatty acids - 2oz EMU Oil For Hair Growth by Hair Thickness Maximizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fat Burner Without Exercise</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/fat-burner-without-exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/fat-burner-without-exercise/</guid>
      <description>The best fat burner without exercise is the one that is right for you.
** The Best Fat Burner Without Exercise **
Cathe Friedrich LITE Metabolic Blast Fat Burner Low Impact Workout DVD For Women - Use This Total Body Exercise DVD To Lose Weight and Burn Fat Without The Impact Lean PM Night Time Fat Burner, Sleep Aid Supplement, &amp;amp; Appetite Suppressant for Men and Women - 60 Stimulant-Free Veggie Weight Loss Diet Pills Goli® Apple Cider Vinegar Gummy Vitamins (1 Pack, 60 Count, Gelatin-Free, Gluten-Free, Vegan &amp;amp; Non-GMO Made with Essential Vitamins B9 &amp;amp; B12) Probiotics 60 Billion CFU - Probiotics for Women, Probiotics for Men and Adults, Natural, Shelf Stable Probiotic Supplement with Organic Prebiotic, Acidophilus Probiotic Turmeric Curcumin with BioPerine 1500mg - Natural Joint &amp;amp; Healthy Inflammatory Support with 95% Standardized Curcuminoids for Potency &amp;amp; Absorption - Non-GMO, Gluten Free Capsules with Black Pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flickering Flameless Candles</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/flickering-flameless-candles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/flickering-flameless-candles/</guid>
      <description>The first thing to consider is the size of the candle. The size of the candle will determine the size of the flame. The size of the flame will determine the size of the flickering light. The size of the flickering light will determine the size of the flame. The size of the flame will determine the size of the flickering light. The size of the flickering light will determine the size of the flame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen Sink Drain</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/kitchen-sink-drain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/kitchen-sink-drain/</guid>
      <description>A kitchen sink drain is a pipe that connects the sink to the sewer or septic system. The drain is usually made of metal, plastic, or PVC.
** The Best Kitchen Sink Drain **
Moen 22036 3-1/2 Inch Kitchen Sink Stainless Steel Basket Strainer with Drain Assembly, Stainless Swan Drain Rack for Kitchen, Triangle Sink Drain Rack Corner Kitchen Sink Strainer Basket, Multi-Function Water Storage Tank Drain Rack Hangs on Faucet, Fits All Sinks DELTA 95B932-30S-SS Lorelai Workstation Kitchen Sink Undermount Stainless Steel Single Bowl with WorkFlow Ledge and Chef’s Kit of 6 Accessories Kitchen Sink Drain 3-1/2 Inch Sink Drain Assembly Kit, Removable Deep Sink Strainer Basket with Sink Stopper/Sealing Lid for Home, Kitchen, Stainless Steel Kitchen Sink Drain Basket Swan Drain Rack, 2 PCS Swan Drain Basket for Kitchen Sink, Multifunctional Kitchen Triangle Sink Filter, Triangle Sink Drain Rack Corner Kitchen Sink Strainer Basket Moen 22036 3-1/2 Inch Kitchen Sink Stainless Steel Basket Strainer with Drain Assembly, Stainless386 ReviewsDrain for stainless sinks Fits sinks with standard 3-5/8” outlet Includes lock nut Stainless finish coordinates with today s popular kitchen appliances and accessoriesFree shippingDetailsSwan Drain Rack for Kitchen, Triangle Sink Drain Rack Corner Kitchen Sink Strainer Basket, Multi-Function Water Storage Tank Drain Rack Hangs on Faucet, Fits All Sinks29 Reviews【Safe material】The Swan Draining Basket is made of food-grade PP material, you can safely use it to wash vegetables and drain water without worrying about harmful substances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemon Essential Oil</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/lemon-essential-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/lemon-essential-oil/</guid>
      <description>The best way to buy lemon essential oil is to buy it from a reputable company.
** The Best Lemon Essential Oil **
NaturoBliss 100% Pure Lemon Essential Oil Therapeutic Grade Premium Quality (4 fl. oz) with Glass Dropper, Perfect for Aromatherapy Handcraft Lemon Essential Oil - 100% Pure and Natural - Premium Therapeutic Grade with Premium Glass Dropper - Huge 4 fl. Oz MAJESTIC PURE Lemon Essential Oil, Therapeutic Grade, Pure and Natural Premium Quality Oil, 4 fl oz Plant Therapy Lemon Essential Oil 30 mL (1 oz) 100% Pure, Undiluted, Natural Aromatherapy, Therapeutic Grade NOW Essential Oils, Lemon Oil, Cheerful Aromatherapy Scent, Cold Pressed, 100% Pure, Vegan, Child Resistant Cap, 4-Ounce SVA 100% Pure Cold Pressed Lemon Essential Oil 4 OZ (118 ML) Virgin/Unrefined For Hair care, Skin care, Aromatherapy Ethereal Nature 100% Pure Oil, Lemon, 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Cave Items</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/man-cave-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/man-cave-items/</guid>
      <description>A man cave is a place where a man can go to escape from the pressures of the outside world. It is a place where he can be himself and do what he wants. It is a place where he can be surrounded by his favorite things. It is a place where he can be alone.
The Best Man Cave Items
Canarm ICH282B05ORB25 Sumerside 5 Light Chandelier, Oil Rubbed Bronze NewAir Beer Froster Refrigerator and Cooler with Glass Door, 125 Can Capacity Freestanding Beer Fridge in Black - Cool to 23 F With Beer and Beverages Frosty In 1 Hour Whiskey Decanter Globe Set with 2 Etched Whiskey Glasses - for Liquor Scotch Bourbon Vodka, Gifts For Men - 850ml NewAir Limited Edition Beverage Refrigerator and Cooler “Beers of the World” with Glass Door, 126 Can Capacity Freestanding Mini Beer Fridge with SplitShelf™ and 7 Temperature Settings AB-1200BC1 Phiestina 24 Inch Beverage Cooler Refrigerator - 175 Can Built-in or Free Standing Beverage Fridge with Glass Door for Soda Beer or Wine - Drink Fridge For Home Bar or Office Abco Tech Indoor Golf Putting Green – Portable Mat with Auto Ball Return Function – Mini Golf Practice Training Aid, Game and Gift for Home, Office, Outdoor Use – 3 Bonus Balls Kodiak Furniture Phoenix Futon, Full, Peter&amp;rsquo;s Cabin Custom Bar Signs For Home Bar - Personalized Neon Signs for Man Cave Game Room - Neon Beer Signs Bar Decor LED Light Sign - Custom Neon Sign Wall Decor - Man Cave LED Bar Light Up Sign Best Choice Products Faux Leather Upholstered Modern Convertible Folding Futon Sofa Bed for Compact Living Space, Apartment, Dorm, Bonus Room w/Removable Armrests, Metal Legs, 2 Cupholders - Black Canarm ICH282B05ORB25 Sumerside 5 Light Chandelier, Oil Rubbed Bronze386 Reviews5 light chain chandelier Oil rubbed bronze finish Requires 5 vintage filament 60 Watt bulbs, Type C (not included)Free shippingDetailsNewAir Beer Froster Refrigerator and Cooler with Glass Door, 125 Can Capacity Freestanding Beer Fridge in Black - Cool to 23 F With Beer and Beverages Frosty In 1 Hour386 Reviews23 DEGREES: COLDEST IN MARKET - At this frosty temperature, your mass market American beer will taste its best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mens Sports Watches</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/mens-sports-watches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/mens-sports-watches/</guid>
      <description>A:
The first thing to consider is the size of the watch.
The second thing to consider is the type of watch.
The third thing to consider is the features of the watch.
The fourth thing to consider is the price of the watch.
The fifth thing to consider is the warranty of the watch.
The sixth thing to consider is the style of the watch.
** The Best Mens Sports Watches **</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jordan Book</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/michael-jordan-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/michael-jordan-book/</guid>
      <description>The best way to find a book is to use the search function on the website.
** The Best Michael Jordan Book **
Michael Jordan: The Life Michael Jordan: The Life386 ReviewsBack Bay BooksFree shippingDetailsDoes Michael Jordan have an autobiography? In his 1998 autobiography For the Love of the Game, Jordan wrote that he was preparing for retirement as early as the summer of 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product For Sweaty Feet</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/product-for-sweaty-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/product-for-sweaty-feet/</guid>
      <description>There are many products on the market that can help with sweaty feet. Some of these products include:
-Antiperspirant
-Antifungal cream
-Antifungal powder
-Antifungal spray
-Antifungal powder
-Antifungal spray
-Antifungal powder
-Antifungal spray
-Antifungal powder
-Antifungal
** The Best Product For Sweaty Feet **
Carpe Antiperspirant Foot Lotion, A dermatologist-recommended solution to stop sweaty, smelly feet, Helps prevent blisters, Great for hyperhidrosis Antihydral Cream - Sweaty to Dry Fingers, Foot, Armpit - Against Strong Perspiration, especially of feet, hand and armpit sweat; Excessive Sweating for Climbers Lotrimin Daily Sweat &amp;amp; Odor Control Medicated Foot Powder, Topical Starch Skin Protectant, 6 Odor-Fighting Ingredients to Control Odor, 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rv Antenna Booster</title>
      <link>https://basement-bar.net/post/rv-antenna-booster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://basement-bar.net/post/rv-antenna-booster/</guid>
      <description>There are many factors to consider when buying an RV antenna booster. The most important factor is the type of RV antenna booster you need. There are two types of RV antenna boosters: roof-mounted and roof-mounted with a mast. The type of RV antenna booster you need will depend on the type of RV antenna you have.
** The Best Rv Antenna Booster **
Winegard RV-WING Wingman UHF RV TV Antenna Booster for the Winegard Sensar Batwing (Digital RV TV Antenna, Easy Installation, Increases Digital UHF TV Reception) - White weBoost Drive Reach RV - Cell Phone Signal Booster kit | Boosts 4G LTE &amp;amp; 5G for All U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
